Dylan Mitchley

I developed my first website back in 2013 and have worked in a host of different industries. I love the mix of logical and creative qualities a Web developer should have. I recently took a coding BootCamp at Hyperion Development where we learnt Full Stack Development (Mongo DB, Express JS, React, Node JS).

Gordon's Bay, Cape Town, South Africa 082 254 1550

dylanmitchley1994@gmail.com https://dmitchley.github.io/resume/ https://github.com/dmitchley

SKILLS AND PROFICIENCIES

- Javascript, HTML, CSS, React, Node JS, Mongo DB
- Teamwork, multitasking, and attention to detail
- Software and web development

LANGUAGES

• English (Native)

WORK HISTORY

UI Designer - Web Developer

Lightly Salted Media | Aug 2013 - Present

I still help run Lightly Salted Media. This is the name of the business I use for my freelance work . I have designed many web & mobile applications and handle front-end web development.

Director of Photography

Various Companies | Jun 2016 - Jul 2020

I have a background in video production so I did on many occasions work as a camera operator or director of photography. I stopped this work because of the covid-19 pandemic destroying the entire industry

Web Design Intern

Red Dot Designs | 2014

My responsibility was to take Photoshop website designs and turn them into html, CSS static websites.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Graphic Design Diploma

Durban Institute of Technology | 2013-2014

Hyperion Development

Full Stack Web Development | 2022 MERN Stack (Mongo DB, Express JS, React JS, Node JS)